Pumpkin Pie Wars is a romance, tv movie film directed by Steven R. Monroe.
Competing bakery owners, Faye McKenzie and Lydia Harper have been feuding for years with the  Lake
Shore County Harvest Festival’s annual pumpkin pie bake-off at the center of it all.
The winner not only gets bragging rights and a trophy, but a
substantial boost to her business, as well.
This year, however, the women are passing the torch to their respective children, Casey and Sam, and
when romantic sparks fly between them, this bake-off promises to be one to remember.
Casey McArthy, played by Julie Gonzalo.
Sam Harper, played by Rico Aragon.
Faye McArthy, played by Michele Scarabelli.
Lydia Harper, played by Jennifer Juniper Angeli.
Reggie McArthy, played by Peter Graham-Gaudreau.
Dee, played by Janet Glassford.
Pumpkin pie is a dessert pie with a spiced, pumpkin-based custard filling.
The pumpkin and pumpkin pie are both a symbol of harvest time, and pumpkin
pie is generally eaten during the fall and early winter.
In the United States and Canada it is usually prepared for Thanksgiving,
Christmas, and other occasions when pumpkin is in season.
Pumpkin is in season generally from mid-October through November.
Harvest occurs during October which is just in time for Thanksgiving.
The pie's filling ranges in color from orange to brown and is baked
in a single pie shell, usually without a top crust.
The pie is generally flavored with pumpkin pie spice, a blend that
includes cinnamon, ginger, nutmeg, and cloves or allspice.
The pie is usually prepared with canned pumpkin, but
fresh-cooked pumpkin can be used.
The film explores themes of autumn, fall season, hallmark.
The tone is emotional.